

## Guilherme Emilio Guain Peixinho Front-end Developer

- ⊠ guilherme.guain@gmail.com
- **(**11) 9 7609-8780

- m guilhermeguain.com.br
- São Paulo, SP Brazil

I've been working with web development since 2012, when I started developing WordPress websites at a communication agency. It took me approximately 8 years to delve into this technology, until in 2020 I decided to migrate and specialize in React.js. I follow principles and practices such as Clean Code and SOLID and my specialty is problem solving.





#### **TECHS & TOOLS**

PRIMARY: React.js, TypeScript, Next.js, ESLint, Git, Tailwind CSS and Postman.

SECONDARY: PHP, Node.js, MySQL, WordPress, AMP, GraphQL, Sass and Gulp.

**DESIGN:** Figma, Photoshop e Illustrator.

#### LANGUAGES

**PORTUGUESE: Native ENGLISH:** Intermediate

# Experience

Health Protection

Front-end Developer 09/2020 - 10/2022









Project developed in Next.js with TypeScript. Among the main tools used in the project are Context API, Axios, Tailwind CSS, Chakra UI, ESLint and React Query. For content management we used Prismic CMS. My activities involved front-end development, integration with APIs, creation of components and pages, maintenance and bug fixing and continuous deployment with Netlify and Vercel.

Toxicologia Pardini

Full-stack Developer 08/2018 - present











Toxicological examination company where I work as a full-stack developer, responsible for developing and maintaining the company's website, in addition to developing integrations with internal systems, CRM and ERP. Among the main activities are SEO optimization, development of new features, bug fixing and website maintenance.

360 Comunicação Digital WordPress Developer 05/2013 - 08/2018







Communication agency where I developed several projects in WordPress, participating in the entire development process, from the creation of the layout to the publication of the website. My activities involved creating and customizing WordPress themes and plugins, optimizing performance and SEO, creating landing pages and integrating with APIs.

### Education

React.js - Ignite ROCKETSEAT	HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and Bootstrap	11/2017 - 02/2018 Online
GoStack - Node.js, React.js and React Native ROCKETSEAT	Programming logic and PHP	10/2012 - 06/2014 São Paulo, SP
Nanodegree Front-end Web Developer	Graphic Design Technician ALPHA CHANNEL	05/2012 - 05/2013 São Paulo, SP